# HYUNJAE WOO

Email & Google Hangouts: hjwoo@umich.edu http://www-personal.umich.edu/~hjwoo/

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest is in the intersection of deep learning and reinforcement learning (RL) and its various real-world applications such as robotics. Specifically, I am interested in building efficient and task-agnostic intelligent machine through hierarchical RL and meta-learning.

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of Michigan - Ann Arbor

Sep 2013 - Present

B.S.E. in Computer Science & Engineering

GPA: 3.3/4.0

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

## Meta Reinforcement Learning with Autonomous Task Inference

Sungryull Sohn, Hyunjae Woo, Jongwook Choi, Honglak Lee

Deep RL Workshop on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2019

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

## Deep Learning Lab @ Univ. of Michigan

Oct 2018 - Present

 $Under graduate\ Research\ Assistant$ 

Advisor: Prof. Honglak Lee

Participated in a research on *meta-hierarchical* RL agent that efficiently and accurately infers the underlying task structure.

#### Reinforcement Learning Lab @ Univ. of Michigan

Oct 2017 - Sep 2018

 $Under graduate\ Researh\ Assistant$ 

Advisor: Prof. Satinder Singh

Participated in a research on StarCraft II Learning Environment using deep (hierarchical) RL agents.

#### Vision and Learning Lab @ Seoul National Univ.

May 2017 - Aug 2017

Summer Research Intern
Advisor: Prof. Gunhee Kim

Participated in a research on *personalized* image captioning and *non-task oriented* (or *conversational*) dialogue systems.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute

Jan 2019 - May 2019

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Participated in a research on improving lane detection accuracy through LiDAR dataset analysis.

#### Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency - Foreign Affairs Dept.

Apr 2014 - Dec 2015

Sergeant

Completed the military duty as an auxiliary-police.

#### SOFTWARE PROJECTS

#### **Automatic Fire Detection**

Developed an object-detection algorithm that detects the instance of fire in the video using YOLO-v2 trained with fire image datasets.

## Facial-Image Sentiment Classification

Analyzed the facial image dataset through K-means algorithm and implemented autoencoder and convolutional neural networks (CNN) for classification.

## Recycle.it

Developed a eco-friendly, camera-based progressive web application using React.js. The application scans a barcode of a product and informs the user with helpful recycling information.

## TSP with Approximation and Optimization Algorithm

Implemented MST approximation and Branch-and-Bound optimization algorithms to several Traveling Salesman Problems (TSP) to create an optimal curcuit path to all the nodes.

## RELEVANT COURSES

Core Courses	Other Courses
EECS498: Reinforcement Learning	MATH217: Linear Algebra
EECS442: Intro to Computer Vision	MATH451: Advanced Calculus
EECS445: Intro to Machine Learning	MATH425: Intro to Probability
EECS492: Intro to Artificial Intelligence	MATH412: Intro to Modern Algebra

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software & Frameworks	Linux/Unix, Tensorflow, PyTorch
Programming Languages	Python, C/C++, C#, Javascript